我们已经提供给你代码，
用于WeatherProvider类的
We've given you codes for the beginnings
of a WeatherProvider class within
扩展ContentProvider在数据包中
the data package that
extends ContentProvider.
Android提供的用来帮助
完成一个ContentProvider的工具之一
One of the tools that Android provides
to help write a ContentProvider
是UriMatcher,
我们会在短时间完成。
is a UriMatcher,
which we are going to write shortly.
填充UriMatcher是在建立ContentProvider
的第三步
Filling out a UriMatcher is the third
step in building our ContentProvider.
ContentProvider实现功能是基于
ContentProviders implement
functionality based upon
URI传递进来。
URIs passed to them.
我们的ContentProvider将实现四种类型的URI
Our ContentProvider will
implement four types of URIs.
每一个URI会分别用于实现
不同类型的操作
Each one of these URIs will be used to
execute different types of operations
针对底层数据库
against the underlying SQL databases.
为了易于实施
For ease of implementation,
ContentProviders通常在内部与每一个URI类型
的整型常量匹配
ContentProviders typically tie each URI type
internally to an integer constant.
这些整型常量已经被添加到提供的
These integer constants have already
been added to the provided
WeatherProvider类
WeatherProvider class.
Android提供了一个URIMathcer类
帮助配对引入的URI
Android provides a UriMatcher
class to help match incoming URIs
与ContentProvider的整型常量。
to the ContentProvider
integer constants.
这是重要的，因为我们需要了解哪一种URI
This is important because we need to
have a way of knowing which type of URI
被传递进了ContentProvider
我们才可以运行请求的操作
is passed into our ContentProvider so
we can perform the requested operation.
当我们有整数常量的时候，
Once we have the integer constants,
我们可以在switch语句中轻易地使用他们。
we can easily use them
in switch statements.
UriMatcher提供了一种表达式语法来匹配不同的URI
UriMatcher provides for an expression
syntax to match various URIs that
有一点像普通表达式的运行方式
works a bit like regular expressions.
#将与数字匹配
Hash symbols will match a number.
*将于字符串匹配
And an asterisk will match any string.
这里是一些例子
Here are some examples